Finding Aid for the The James D. Squires Papers
Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I: Journalism career (1972-1989)
  - Chicago Tribune - Chicago (1981-1989)
    - Box 15: Letters to editor, outgoing correspondence
      - Outgoing correspondence, January 6, 1989-January 16, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Box 16: Outgoing correspondence, phone messages
      - Outgoing correspondence, January 17, 1989-January 31, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Outgoing correspondence, February 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Outgoing correspondence, March 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Outgoing correspondence, April 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Outgoing correspondence, May 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Outgoing correspondence, June 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Outgoing correspondence, July 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Outgoing correspondence, August 1, 1989-August 17, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Outgoing correspondence, August 18, 1989-August 28, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Outgoing correspondence, August 30, 1989-August 31, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Outgoing correspondence, September 1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Outgoing correspondence, October 1989 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Outgoing correspondence, November 1989-December 1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Outgoing correspondence, n.d. [1989] (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Phone messages, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Phone messages, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Phone messages, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Phone messages, n.d. [1984-1985] (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Phone messages, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Box 17: Phone messages, weekly agendas
      - Phone messages, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Phone messages, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Phone messages, n.d. [1987] (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Phone messages, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Phone messages, February 1989-September 1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Phone messages, October 1989-December 1989 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Phone messages, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Weekly agendas, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Weekly agendas, January 1985-March 1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Weekly agendas, April 1985-June 1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Weekly agendas, July 1985-August 1985 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Weekly agendas, September 1985-October 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Weekly agendas, November 1985-December 1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Weekly agendas, January 1986-February 1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Weekly agendas, March 1986 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Weekly agendas, April 5, 1986-April 21, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Weekly agendas, April 27, 1986-June 7, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Weekly agendas, June 16, 1986-July 1986 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Weekly agendas, August 1986-September 1986 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Weekly agendas, October 1986-December 1986 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Weekly agendas, January 1987-February 1987 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Weekly agendas, March 1987-April 1987 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Weekly agendas, May 1987-June 1987 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Box 18: Weekly agendas
      - Weekly agendas, July 1987-August 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Weekly agendas, September 1987-October 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Weekly agendas, November 1987-December 1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Weekly agendas, January 1988-February 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Weekly agendas, March 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Weekly agendas, April 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Weekly agendas, May 1988-June 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Weekly agendas, July 1988-August 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Weekly agendas, September 1988-October 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Weekly agendas, November 1988-December 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Weekly agendas, January 1989-February 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Weekly agendas, March 1989-April 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Weekly agendas, May 1989-June 1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Weekly agendas, July 1989-August 1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Weekly agendas, September 1989-October 1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Weekly agendas, November 1989-December 1989 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Speeches (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Notes, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Notes, 1989; n.d. [1988] (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Box 19: Clippings, publications
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, January 1984-August 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, October 1984-December 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, January 1985-March 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Clippings, April 1985-September 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Clippings, January 1989-April 1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Clippings, May 1989-September 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, October 1989-December 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Publications, Avenue M January 1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Publications, Brief on behalf of Chicago Tribune Co. 1986 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Publications, The Bulletin June/July 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Publications, The Bulletin November/December 1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Publications, The Bulletin November/December 1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Publications, The Bulletin January 1986 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Box 20: Publications, press releases, photographs, miscellaneous
      - Publications, Chicago July 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Publications, Chicago Times Magazine July/August 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Publications, Columbia Journalism Review June 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Publications, Columbia Journalism Review July/August 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Publications, Columbia Journalism Review January/February 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Publications, Columbia Journalism Review July/August 1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Publications, Donald G. Herzberg Memorial Fund Lecture given by John Chancellor at Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism, December 3, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Publications, Harper’s Magazine May 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Publications, Little Trib June/July 1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Publications, Minorities and the Tribune SRG Report (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Publications, The National Leader August 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Publications, The New Republic February 10, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Publications, Nieman Reports Summer 1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Publications, Nieman Reports Spring 1989 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Publications, The Quill September 1985 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Publications, Trib Data-Link January 16, 1984; April 9, 1984; November 26, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Publications, Washington Journalism Review July 1985 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Press releases (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Photographs (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous, Dummy mocks of Chicago Tribune, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous, Russia trip notes, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous, Russia trip souvenirs and receipts, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Box 21: Miscellaneous, original clippings
      - Miscellaneous, Russia trip postcards, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, Russia trip briefing materials, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, Gridiron Dinner, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous - n.d. (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous - n.d. (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Original clippings, December 13, 1983-March 31, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Original clippings, April 2, 1985-January 31, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Original clippings, February 24, 1986-April 3, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Original clippings, April 3, 1987-May 5, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Original clippings, May 12, 1989-November 24, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Original clippings, December 9, 1989-December 15, 1989; n.d. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Series II: Ross Perot campaign - RESTRICTED (1992-1995)
    - Box 22: Incoming correspondence
      - Incoming correspondence - Allen, Meg-Bayse, Jennifer (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Bell, Sally-Bolan, Thomas (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Bond, Rich (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Brickman, Gary-Cahill, Carol (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Canzeri, Joe (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Chancellor, John-Faria, Paula (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Fisher, Richard (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence - Frost, Bill-Goldberg, Howard (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence - Goodwin, Dick-Hoffman, Eric (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence - Hollander, Richard-Hume, Ellen (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence - Jarvie, Charles-Jordan, DeSoto (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence - Jordan, Hamilton (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kandel, Edward-Leventhal, Michael (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Incoming correspondence - Lindsley, Hays-Los Angeles Times (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Incoming correspondence - Luce, Tom (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Incoming correspondence - Lurie, Cheryl-Luntz, Frank (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Incoming correspondence - Maas, Liz-McCoole, Muffie (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Incoming correspondence - McGrath, Ellie-Meyerson, David (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Incoming correspondence - Meyerson, Morton-Overby, Charles (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Incoming correspondence - Parkhurst, David-Peck, Bob (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Incoming correspondence - Perot, Ross (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Incoming correspondence - Pincus, Ted-Proctor, B. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Box 23: Incoming correspondence, outgoing correspondence, phone messages
      - Incoming correspondence - Rafshoon, Gerald-Rowe, Susan (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Royko, Mike-Seidenburg, Donald (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Smith, Barbara-Thompson, Kathryn (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Waldman, Gene-Zuckerman, Al (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Unidentified (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Outgoing correspondence, May 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Outgoing correspondence, June 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Outgoing correspondence, July 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. to Sally Bell (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. to campaign team (includes one or more: Tom Luce, Morton Meyerson, Ross Perot, Hamilton Jordan, Ed Rollins) (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. to Ross Perot (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Outgoing correspondence - n.d. to Ross Perot (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Phone messages, April 1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Phone messages, May 1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Phone messages, June 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Phone messages, July 1992-August 1992 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Phone messages, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Box 24: Campaign material, statements, speeches
      - Campaign staff information (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Campaign strategy and agendas (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Campaign strategy and agendas (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Advertising strategy (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Federal budget ideas (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Issue papers (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Issue papers (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Interview requests and schedules (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Press releases (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Statements (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Statements (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Speeches - given by Tom Luce (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Speeches - given by Ross Perot early campaign speech during Perot Petition Campaign [possibly aired on CNN] beginning, “A few months ago on a television show, I told the American people that if they would climb into the political arena with me, I’d run as an independent candidate for president.” (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Speeches - given by Ross Perot to the NAACP Presidential Council meeting on July 11, 1992 at the Nashville Convention Center (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Speeches - draft for speech to the NAACP Presidential Council meeting, rejected by Ross Perot (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Speeches - given by James Squires at St. Mary’s [late 1992] (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Speeches - multiple unidentified (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Speeches - multiple unidentified (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Box 25: Rebuilding America, transcripts, quote notebook
      - Rebuilding America, June 21, 1992 version, notes (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Rebuilding America, July 3, 1992 outline, notes (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Rebuilding America, July 8, 1992 version (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Rebuilding America, July 14, 1992 version (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Rebuilding America - final version (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Interview transcripts, April 26, 1988-May 13, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Interview transcripts, CSPAN interview taped May 14, 1992, aired May 17, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Interview transcripts, May 28, 1992-June 11, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Interview transcript, June 11, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Interview transcripts, July 9, 1992-July 17, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Interview transcripts, July 17, 1992-May 4, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Quote notebook - Abortion-Crime (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Quote notebook - Deficit-Economy (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Quote notebook - Education-Equal Rights (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Quote notebook - Foreign Policy-Middle East (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Quote notebook - Science and Technology-Urban Problems (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Box 26: Congressional testimony, polls, notes
      - Testimony, House Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs - Committee on Foreign Affairs, October 15, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs, July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs (exhibits), July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Testimony, Senate Select Committee on POW-MIA Affairs (exhibits), July 1, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Polls and surveys Black, Gordon S. “The Politics of American Discontent: A Study of Voter Discontent.”, June 3, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Polls and surveys Times Mirror Center for the People & the Press. “The People, The Press & Politics 1990: A Times Mirror Political Typology.”, September 19, 1990. (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Polls and surveys Times Mirror Center for the People & the Press. “The People, The Press & Politics Campaign ’92 Electability: Bush, Clinton & Congress Survey IV.”, April 3, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Polls and surveys, Times Mirror Center for the People & the Press. “The Press & the Campaign: Part II; Times Mirror News Interest Index.” September 1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Polls and surveys - miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Polls and surveys - miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Notes (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Notes (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Notes (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Box 27: Notes, unidentified manuscript, article draft, subject files, photograph, clippings
      - Notes (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Notes (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified manuscript by James Squires (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Notes and draft for Rolling Stone article, published, October 1, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Subject file - Nixon Project Papers (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Subject file - United We Stand America correspondence (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Subject file, United We Stand America Convention, August 1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Subject file, United We Stand America Convention, August 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Subject file, United We Stand America Convention, August 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Photograph (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Clippings (database), September 3, 1986-April 25, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Clippings (database), May 14, 1987-November 19, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Clippings (database), 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Clippings, February 1992-March 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Clippings, April 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Clippings (database), April 8, 1992-June 22, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Clippings, May 2, 1992-May 15, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Clippings, May 16, 1992-May 22, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Clippings, May 25, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Clippings, May 26, 1992-May 29, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Clippings, June 4, 1992-June 8, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Box 28: Clippings, clipping notebook assembled by Jack Gordon, publications
      - Clippings, June 11, 1992-June 18, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, June 21, 1992-June 29, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, July 1, 1992-July 3, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, July 5, 1992-July 11, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, July 13, 1992-July 26, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, August 25, 1992-November 21, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Clippings, November 8, 1994-February 6, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Clippings - n.d. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Clipping notebook (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Clipping notebook (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Clipping notebook (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Clipping notebook (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Clipping notebook (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Publications, Alger, Dean. “The Media, the Public and the Development of Candidates’ Images in the 1992 Presidential Election.” October 1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Publications, The Bulletin November 1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Publications, Campbell, Karlyn Kohrs. “Shadowboxing with Stereotypes: The Press, the Public, and the Candidates’ Wives.” July 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Publications, Clinton, Bill. “Putting People First: A National Economic Strategy for America” (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Publications, Cronkite, Walter. Theodore H. White Lecture. Joan Shorenstein Barone Center on the Press, Politics and Public Policy, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University. November 15, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Publications, Dennis, Everette E., Martha FitzSimon, John Pavlik, Seth Rachlin, Dirk Smillie, David Stebenne, Mark Thalhimer. “Covering the Presidential Primaries.” June 1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Publications, Dennis, Everette E., Martha FitzSimon, John Pavlik, Seth Rachlin, Dirk Smillie, David Stebenne, Mark Thalhimer. “The Finish Line: Covering the Campaign’s Final Days.” January 1993 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Box 29: Publications
      - Publications, Dennis, Everette E., Martha FitzSimon, John Pavlik, Seth Rachlin, Dirk Smillie, David Stebenne, Mark Thalhimer. “The Homestretch: New Politics. New Media. New Voters?” October 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Publications, Goodwin, Richard N. “Promises to Keep: A Call for a New American Revolution.” May 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Publications, Grossman, Lawrence K. “Reflections on Television’s Role in American Presidential Elections.” January 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Publications, Harper’s July 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Publications, Hotline June 1, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Publications, Hotline June 2, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Publications, Hotline June 3, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Publications, Hotline June 4, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Publications, Hotline June 5, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Publications, Hotline June 8, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Publications, Hotline June 9, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Publications, Hotline June 10, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Publications, Hotline June 11, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Publications, Hotline June 12, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Publications, Hotline June 15, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Publications, Hotline June 16, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Publications, Hotline June 17, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Publications, Hotline June 24, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Publications, Hotline June 25, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Publications, Hotline June 26, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Publications, Hotline June 29, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Publications, Hotline June 30, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Publications, Hotline July 1, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Publications, Hotline July 2, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Publications, Hotline July 6, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Publications, Hotline July 8, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Publications, Hotline July 9, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Publications, Hotline July 14, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Publications, Hotline July 15, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Box 30: Publications, miscellaneous items, original clippings
      - Publications - Menendez, Albert J. “Who Voted for Perot?” p. 42-60 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Publications - Menendez, Albert J. “Who Voted for Perot?” p. 61-68, Part III p. 1-15 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Publications - Menendez, Albert J. “Who Voted for Perot?” Part III p. 16-40 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Publications - Menendez, Albert J. “Who Voted for Perot?” Part III p. 41-65 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Publications - Menendez, Albert J. “Who Voted for Perot?” Part III p. 66-74, Part IV p. 157-170 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Publications - Menendez, Albert J. “Who Voted for Perot?” Part IV p. 171-196 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Publications, Nieman Reports Fall 1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Publications, New York Times Magazine June 28, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Publications, Newsweek July 20, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Publications, Newsweek November 9, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Publications, The Perot Initiative June 1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Publications, Rolling Stone October 1, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Publications, Senior Chronicle July 1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Publications, Time July 20, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)